Hi. Hi.
How are you?
All good, and you?
Pretty crazy with the AI stuff. Yeah, Experimenting a lot.
I saw your screenshots. I'm like, I don't. I don't get this yet. Yeah. But I mean it.
I think it's kind of pretty hectic for everyone, but I wanted to have a quick scene with everyone on
the tech team. I already want. I'll give you like a brief overview.
I'm not part of the SEC team, Emily.
Yeah, but you're in the meeting, so you will know before anyone else, so.
Okay. Okay, got it.
I mean, I'm just double checking with everyone who joins the meeting. So
basically what I'm trying to work on is to lock a potential day for global summit.
And as you already know, we were trying to also do like a second summit this year to be like
pod focus for.
I mean, one of the things that makes sense to have as a pot summit would be with engineering.
So basically we are thinking on doing one like that team summit, finalizing quarter two. That's around.
You mentioned engineering. Yeah, the engineering team. Okay. Yeah.
So it would be like after wrapping up fundraising series B.
So it's going to be around May and June this year.
And for Global Summit, we are kind of thinking about Q4 similar dates at last year, something around October and
November, so that it's not high season yet. Because we did our like last summit was during high season.
So yeah, that's basically what we are thinking on.
Just to give you like a super high level overview of it.
It's kind of a draft right now, but I'm just working on getting like a sense of availability of the
team. So I'm gonna send you in some shot spreadsheet similar as I did last time.
When I gather everyone's availability to lock the dates, you will see that we have a tab for Q2 and
for Q4 just to, I mean for engineering team. We are still like on tbd, who will join that?
But I think it worth it to have your availability as well on that one and for Q4, like, you
know, everyone will let me know because we want to short down the options of potential dates for Global Summit
so we can lock a date for that one as well. Yes.
Okay. So I basically have to answer to both of them just in case. Okay. Okay.
Also the default one is free. I just have to change. Okay, great.
Yeah, default is free.
And if you are not available in any of those states, you mark as not available or not ideal or
to be confirmed. Just. Just in case if you cannot do it live.
Like if you need to review anything, I will follow up with you tomorrow or on Friday because based on
this, I will ship the rapid doc with the options and like the proposal in terms of what, what, what's
like best to do in this scenario. So yeah, I mean, that would be it.
That's what I need from you guys so far. And any other thoughts, any other like, you know,
suggestions you can have for this planning. Super helpful. I.
I talked with Evgeny earlier today and I asked him about maybe like including support team for this engineering summit
and he was like, maybe it makes sense for Anne.
But he was like, maybe it doesn't make sense for her to be the whole week or I don't know,
like we should be thinking about it.
I think it makes sense for you to be there because you, you work closely with Evgeny and it's also
an opportunity to, you know, collaborating person, which is not like the regular thing.
So I mean, that's why I included you here because I think that even though we don't do like a
support summit. You could be included in this one as well, so.
So I think it makes sense given it's going to be like focus on kind of engineering and this product
design team. And I know that you, you know, you are, you, you work closely with, with those two pods.
So yeah, I think that that makes sense like potentially. So. Yeah.
Another possible option for this team summit is to doing it during planning, either retro or planning week.
Because given we are going to have like bots, like, like product bots there, it could be good time to
work on roadmap together. So that's another interesting option there.
You mean the engineering one?
Yeah.
So Ben is, is going.
Okay. Yeah. Because if you have like product and Dorothy potentially.
Yes. Since she's transitioning to work on Prado. So. Yeah.
Okay. So all these people in this list are people that we are considering to, to send.
Except of course all the engineers that should be there already. Yeah.
Charlie.
Huh? Okay, got it. Okay. I think cycle planning is a good option for sure.
Yeah.
Mm.
I think that the opportunity to do like a product focus summit, you know, like go like do like an
intensive week in terms of product with dives and that kind of stuff.
Mm. Mm. Okay. I think I'll finish this like 10 minutes or so. I'll just check with my husband.
Oh well, another thing for the Q4, the general one, I should consider only my own matters.
Even though I don't have to ask my team anything or should I already cover them in some way?
No, just me only your availability.
And then when we have the shortlist of the dates, I will ship an announcement to the whole team so
they let us know which of the shortlist of dates they are available.
Makes sense. Okay, great. You do.
Okay. Thank you again for making the time to meet and. Yeah, keep me posted once you fill this out.
Thank you.
Okay, we do. Thank you. Bye. Bye.
Bye.